# JP Nuyens

Web Developer | Graphic Designer | Videographer

- 555 Anand Pvt.
- JP.Nuyens16@gmail.com
- Ottawa, Ont. K1V 2R7
- · 613-868-2391



www.jpdynamic.com

# **Profile**

A highly motivated and creative professional who is flexible, organized, and a quick learner.

Three years of self-directed learning while also working as a Junior IT associate followed by attending Algonquin College for the Interactive Media Management program.

Developed many essential skills such as project management, troubleshooting, time management, and focusing on simultaneous requests to meet project deadlines.

# **Relevant Experience**

#### Junior IT associate

Rowland and Associates (Jan 2015 - Present) - Ottawa, Ont.

- Worked with various clients from private companies to governmental departments in order to provide IT support in a variety of areas.
- Identified website issues and revamped existing structure while integrating improved functionality through plug-ins and applications.
- Researched equipment specs and costs so as to acquire, configure, and implement a new office infrastructure with 8 new Windows PCs for Vets Without Borders.
- Supported clients to resolve troubleshooting issues with web hosting, servers, and hardware.

# Other Experience

#### Research Technician

Apoptosis Research Centre at CHEO (Oct 2010 - Oct 2014) - Ottawa, Ont.

- Investigated the mechanisms in which cancer cells evade cell death, and promote accelerated cancer cell growth. Attempted to induce cell death in various cancer cell lines synergistically with various chemical compounds and cytokines.
- Conducted and coordinated multiple experiments in order to meet project goals and deadlines.
- Provided training and mentoring to numerous students to streamline productivity and increase efficiency of numerous projects.



## **Technical Skills**

Comfortable with Wordpress, Bootstrap, and Foundation.

Knowledge of Google Analytics and best practices in Responsive Web Design.

Constant drive to improve and adapt to an ever changing technological landscape.

Web Design • Dreamweaver	Graphic Design • Illustrator	CMS • Wordpress	Web Frameworks • Bootstrap
<ul> <li>Sublime text</li> </ul>	<ul><li>Photoshop</li></ul>	<ul><li>Drupal</li></ul>	<ul><li>Foundation</li></ul>
Brackets	<ul><li>Indesign</li><li>Flash/Animate</li></ul>	• Joomla	• Skeleton
Operating Systems • Windows	Languages • HTML5	Video/Audio • Premiere Pro	Miscellaneous • Word
<ul><li>Apple/iOS</li></ul>	• CSS	<ul> <li>After Effects</li> </ul>	<ul><li>Excel</li></ul>
<ul> <li>Ubuntu</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Javascript</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Audition</li> </ul>	<ul><li>Outlook</li></ul>
• Linux	• PHP	<ul><li>Final Cut</li></ul>	<ul><li>Powerpoint</li></ul>
<ul><li>Fedora</li></ul>	• SQL	<ul><li>iMovie</li></ul>	
	• XML		
	• jQuery		

# **Education**

#### Algonquin College

Interactive Media Management Graduate Certificate Program (Sep 2015 - Apr 2016)
 4.00 GPA - made the Dean's List for exceptional student achievements.

### **University of Ottawa**

• B.Sc. Biochemistry (2005 - 2008)

### **University of Ottawa**

• B.Sc. Biology (2001 - 2005)

# **Affiliations**

- Attended Drupal Camp Ottawa
- Part of Wordpress Meetup group

# **Interests**

- Captain of numerous Dodgeball and Ultimate frisbee teams while playing at a competitive level.
- Competing in a national tournament to become part of the national team for Dodgeball Canada.

# References

• Available upon request

